<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>people on mediating media arts</title>
    <link>https://mediating.github.io/tags/people/</link>
    <description>Recent content in people on mediating media arts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://mediating.github.io/tags/people/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Min-hyung Kang</title>
      <link>https://mediating.github.io/people/people/people-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mediating.github.io/people/people/people-3/</guid>
      <description>Who are you, where do you live and work? I am Min-hyung kang, living and working in South Korea, temporarily staying in Berlin now for my curatorial fellowship.
How would you define mediating media arts / media art mediation? When media becomes a powerful tool beyond its original definition of mediating, there comes a series of consequences that we need to take a look. It is merely an artistic tool now, and definition must be made from revisiting conventional media art in a political, socioenonomicanol, historical and communal way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hanna Hirakawa</title>
      <link>https://mediating.github.io/people/people/people-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mediating.github.io/people/people/people-4/</guid>
      <description>Who are you, where do you live and work? I am Hanna Hirakawa. Curator at the Idemitsu Museum of Arts, specializing in Japanese Edo Period Art. I also work on independent projects that deal with archives and contemporary art in Asia concerned with its (colonial) history and sociopolitical issues. Translator and interpreter in the field of contemporary art. Shorter version: Hanna Hirakawa. Curator at the Idemitsu Museum of Arts. Works on independent projects dealing with archives and contemporary art in Asia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Youjin Jeon</title>
      <link>https://mediating.github.io/people/people/people-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mediating.github.io/people/people/people-2/</guid>
      <description>Who are you, where do you live and work? Hello, I’m Youjin Jeon from Seoul, working as a composer and media artist, and now I’m running a community called WOMAN OPEN TECH LAB.
How would you define mediating media arts / media art mediation? Our society is kind of obsessed with learning and presenting new, emerging, cutting-edge technologies. Mediation is an attempt to overcome or bypass the many problems and limitations of the existing educational process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shirley Hendrikse</title>
      <link>https://mediating.github.io/people/people/people-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mediating.github.io/people/people/people-9/</guid>
      <description>Who are you, where do you live and work? I am Shirley Hendrikse, Head of Education at STRP in Eindhoven, The Netherlands. Since 2006, STRP explores the relationshop between art, technology, and societal issues with artists, designers, media makers, thinkers, and its audience.
How would you define mediating media arts / media art mediation? What specific issues and concerns do you have in the field of education and technology? For us, media art mediation is the engagement of specific target groups in the field of media art, or, as STRP refers to, Art &amp;amp; Technology.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
